http://www.bransondailynews.com/site/privacy.html

Site
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for requesting information, will only be used to send you information and updates at your request.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Online Privacy ProtectionBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions, therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.All users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.http://www.bransontrilakesnews.cominternet@bransontrilakesnews.com417-334-3161
Would you favor a mandatory face covering ordinance in the city of Branson
The Branson Board of Aldermen on Thursday (now postponed to July 28)
will consider an ordinance that would require face coverings in public spaces. The aldermen might approve it, disapprove it, or approve an amended version. Would you be in favor of some form of mandatory face covering ordinance in the city of Branson?
You voted:
Yes
No
Vote
View Results
Back
Newsletters
Success! An email has been sent to
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
News Updates
Would you like to receive our daily news? Signup today!
Manage your lists
Real Estate
Lot for Sale $100. Emerald Point Phase 9, Lot
FOR SALE 3BR/2BA
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesCrane man killed in Sunday shooting, suspect in custodyFour Stone Co. residents arrested for child endangermentChoices Concert Hall to close, final night of music set for Dec. 19Long-awaited Branson aquarium is now openBranson Chief discusses face coveringsFour more die of COVID-19 in Taney County, two in StoneChristmas with The Duttons: Family talks the holidays, the next generation, the impacts of 2020Annual Adoration Parade and Nativity scene lighting returns SundayThe Collingsworth Family Christmas Tour to stop in BransonFederal charges dismissed against duck employees due to lack of jurisdiction
Images
Videos
CommentedAldermen hear potential changes to animal ordinance (4)Tourism Tax to see April ballot (2)Taney County Court scales back to Phase 1 due to positive COVID case (1)Branson Chief discusses face coverings (1)Bull Creek debuts new fluffy mayor, new village hall (1)Area singer, actress dies from COVID-19 complications (1)
Stocks
Market Data by TradingView
© Copyright 2020 Branson Tri-Lakes News, 200 Industrial Park Drive Hollister, MO | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
